My name's Ron Kepple, and a couple of years ago, I backed my
wife's car into a concrete wall-
Oof
... and tore the rear quarter up pretty good.
She was not happy on that one.
No, she was not.
I had one-
I heard about it every day
I did, yeah
Brought it over here to Phil's just on a hunch.
Couldn't believe how surprised I was, how satisfied we were.
They want you to be happy. They don't want to pass something off that their
customers aren't happy with. First thing I noticed when I came in here is what a
great mood everybody is in, all the time.
From the girls at the front, to the shop, right up to Ed.
And people who are happy do good work.
They've done a couple little things for me, and did a great job.
My wife's car was actually a custom color.
Oh.
It was a metal flake black,
and they blended it in. You could not tell that
anything had ever happened to that car.
Right.
And I got a great price to do the work.
They walked me through every step of the process.
They showed me what they were doing.
They touched up things that didn't need to be touched up because they wanted it to
look good when it rolled out of here, and that says a lot.
I can't say enough about the service that you get here.
They want you, and I keep saying that, they want you to be
tickled to death. I've got my other car here today, as a matter of fact, to have
Ed take a look at a scratch on the rear quarter again.
Okay.
And I would highly recommend
Phil's Collision to everybody. Nobody's going to work on my cars.
Wow.
I've got a '68 Chevy Impala convertible that needed a little
touch-up here and there, and it's,
again, a custom color, a rare color, and they matched it
perfect. Absolutely perfect.
Oh, yeah.
I couldn't be happier. Could not be happier.